Büşra Aljasem

Computer Engineer

Contact

Address

Ankara

Phone

+905388245278

E-mail

bushra.aljasseem@gmail.co

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bushra-aljasem-7998171

Skills

JavaScript programming

HTML5/CSS3

PHP/Laravel /Codeigniter

Mern Stack

Node is

React is / Redux

Vue js / vuex /Vutify / Axios

Bootstrap/Tailwind

.NET Framework · Microsoft SQL Server · C#

JSON Web Token (JWT)

Mysql/MongoDB

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 5 years of related experience.

Work History

2022-03 -2022-07

Web Application Specialist

Tailor Made Excel, London

- Collaborated with marketing, representing web team to establish projects goals, projections and milestones.
- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages, plugins and functionality for continuous improvement.
- Develop companion application programming interface (API) for web apps.

2021-01 -2022-03

Full Stack Web Developer

Nanomedya, Ankara

- Developed efficient and maintainable software according to business objectives and needs of clients.
- Used WordPress CMS to develop Seo-friendly Websites.
- Build WordPress themes from scratch according to clients' needs.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues
- Discussed project progress with customers, collected feedback on different stages and directly addressed concerns.

2019-07 -2021-01

Full Stack Web Developer

Birbölüiki Bilişim Ajansı, Ankara

- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Related frameworks such as Bootstrap Tailwind, React js, Vue js.
- Alternated between frontend and backend development duties, fulfilling Full Stack development commitments on company projects.



2018-01 -2019-01

Junior Web Developer

ARTMENTAL, Ankara

- Maintained advanced knowledge of several programming languages.
- Built website interfaces with HTML and CSS.
- Developed page layouts and navigation tools that met or exceeded user expectations.
- Applied knowledge of JavaScript and Object-Oriented Programming to create successful interactive designs.
- Built and styled new mobile-friendly websites, transitioning legacy presentations to simultaneous easy-to-use versions.

2014-09 -2016-12

Software Engineer

Syrian Ministry Of Tourism, Damascus

- E-government portal development.
- Participated in architecture, design and implementation of back-end features using C# Language.

Education

2017-01 -2020-01

M.D.: Computer Engineering

Kırıkkale Üniversitesi - Kırıkkale/ Turkey

- Security in IOT Networks Thesis
- IoT Security Issues, Threats, and Defenses
- 3.25 GPA

2009-01 -2014-01

Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering

Ittihad University - Damascus / Syria

- Bachelor's degree in Computer engineering
- 3.15 GPA